How to marry a billionaire.
Chalet Girl is a comedy, romance film directed by Phil Traill.
While working a job at an exclusive ski resort to support her Dad, Kim learns to snowboard
and is so good at it that she enters a competition with a huge cash prize.
She has to dig deep to overcome her fears, but her life gets more
complicated through her spoken-for boss, Jonny.
Kim Matthews, played by Felicity Jones.
Jonny Madsen, played by Ed Westwick.
Caroline Madsen, played by Brooke Shields.
Richard Madsen, played by Bill Nighy.
Georgie, played by Tamsin Egerton.
Bill Matthews, played by Bill Bailey.
Chalet Girl is a 2011 romantic comedy sports film directed by Phil Traill.
The film stars Felicity Jones and Ed Westwick in the lead roles and also features Ken Duken,
Tamsin Egerton, Sophia Bush, Bill Bailey, Brooke Shields, and Bill Nighy.
Written by Tom Williams, the film was produced by Pippa Cross,
Harriet Rees, Dietmar Guentsche, and Wolfgang Behr.
Chalet Girl was filmed on location in Sankt Anton am Arlberg,
Austria, and in Garmisch-Partenkirchen, Germany.
While critical reaction to the film was mixed, Jones' performance was praised.
The film grossed US$5.5 million worldwide against an
£8 million (US$13 million) budget.
The film explores themes of competition,
snowboarding, austria, birthday party, chalet.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.